techandall.com 2014-10-13

# Tech & ALL Privacy Policy | Tech & ALL – PSD, Tech News, and other resources for free

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**What information do we collect?  **  
We collect information from you when you register on our site. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do we use your information for?  **  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: – To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) – To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) – To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) – To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature – To send periodic emails. The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

**How do we protect your information?  **  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?  **  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  **  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links  **  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  **  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only  **  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent  **  
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy  **  
We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. It is your responsibility to review this Policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms.

**Advertising  
**We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Contacting Us  **  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. [http://www.TechandALL.com](http://www.techandall.com/)
